https://www.philadelphiaeagles.com/footer/privacy-policy

Last Updated: September 25, 2020
Philadelphia Eagles, LLC ("Philadelphia Eagles", "we," "our," "us") respects your privacy and values your trust and confidence. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to our websites www.philadephiaeagles.com, www.lincolnfinancialfield.com, www.flyeaglesfly.com and online services such as our Eagles Official Mobile and Philadelphia Eagles for iPad mobile applications that link to or post this Privacy Polic­­­­y (collectively, the "Services"), and explains how we collect, use, and disclose information through the Services. By using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that is collected or obtained through sites or services that do not link to this Privacy Policy (including the Team Shop) or information collected by the National Football League ("NFL") or the other member clubs (the "Member Clubs").
If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy or practices please contact us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at
https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request
To check the Philadelphia Eagles' status with our third party privacy certification programs, please click here.
1. Information Collection
You generally are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit the Services. However, we may ask you for some or all of the following types of information when you register with our Services, sign up for contests or sweepstakes, use a send-to-a-friend feature, participate in surveys, access various content or features, submit comments or content, or directly contact us with questions or feedback:
o Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, and mobile number;
o Unique identifiers, such as a user name or password;
o Demographic information, such as gender, date of birth or age;
o Financial information, such as credit card or other payment information;
o Device Information, such as Operating system version and type and device carrier;
o Geolocation information;
o Communications preferences;
o Search queries;
o Comments and other information posted in our interactive online forums and chat rooms;
o Correspondence and other information that you send to us; and
o Additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
We also may collect certain information automatically when you visit the Services, including:
o Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
o Other unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers;
o Your browser type and operating system;
o Sites you visited before and after visiting the Services;
o Pages you view and links you click on within the Services;
o Information collected through cookies, web beacons, local shared objects, and other technologies;
o Information about your interactions with e-mail messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were received, opened, or forwarded; and
o Standard Server Log Information.
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by us and our partners such as sponsors, advertisers, affiliates, and other service providers (such as e-commerce, analytics and customer service support). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.
We use local storage objects (LSOs) such as Flash or HTML 5 to store content information and preferences
Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use LSOs to collect and store information.
Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application.
2. Use of Information
We may use information that we collect through the Services for a variety of purposes, including to:
o Provide you with the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information you request and respond to correspondence that we receive from you;
o Contact you via email and otherwise about your account, products, services, contests, and events that we think might be of interest to you;
o Send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.
o Contact you via push notifications based on location with Philadelphia Eagles news, news regarding the application or updates to features of the application. You may opt-out of push notifications by visiting your application settings or at the device level.
o Send you text alerts on team news and promotions if you opt-in to receive this communication. You may opt-out of text alerts by replying "STOP" to cancel this service.,
o Maintain or administer the Services, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer;
o We collect your geolocation information for the purpose of providing you with information based on where you are located; we may share your geolocation data with third parties for the purpose of them serving you ads for activities or promotions in your area. If you do not want your geolocation information to be shared, you may opt out by contacting us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com.
o Publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features;
o Customize and personalize your use of the Services; and
o As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
o If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site or services, we will ask for your friend's name and email address, to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.
o
3. Sharing of Information
We are committed to maintaining your trust, and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share the information we collect.
o Service Providers: We may share your personal information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf (such as to host the Services, fulfill orders, provide products and services, manage databases; perform analyses, process credit card payments, provide customer service, or send communications for us). These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
o Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We may share your personal information with Eagles Charitable Foundation, Eagles Autism Challenge and with all members of the NFL Family, including, without limitation, NFL Properties LLC, NFL International LLC, NFL Enterprises LLC, NFL Ventures, L.P., and NFL Ventures, Inc.
o Select Business Partners:With your permission, we may share your personal information with select business partners so that they can provide you with special offers, promotional materials, and other materials that may be of interest to you. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to have certain information shared with our third party business partners when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or elect to receive marketing offers or other information. If you do not elect to have your information shared, it will not be shared with such third parties. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their own purposes. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these partners, please contact us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com.
o Co-Branding Partners: We may receive or share personal information about you from our co-branding partners. When a co-branding relationship exists, Philadelphia Eagles information and branding will be present along with the branding of our business partners or sponsors. In these instances, any personal information that you choose to share is voluntary and you agree that your information may be used by us as well as by our co-branding partner. If you have any questions about the use of your personal information in these instances, please contact us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com.
o Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. This information is used to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising or to manage your preferences you may do so here: http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/.
o Business Transfer: If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, a business reorganization, or similar event, we may transfer your personal information as part of such transaction.
o Administrative or Legal Process: We may disclose your information to third parties when we believe that disclosure is necessary in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of our organization, our corporate affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, and the users of our Services; enforce our Terms of Use; respond to and resolve claims or complaints; investigate or prevent fraud or for risk management purposes; and comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity, whether or not legally required.
o Interactive Features: We may share information with third parties when you post information to a user profile or a public area of the Services, such as a chat room, forum, blog, or other community tool. If you post to these interactive features, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. Any information you provide in these areas of the Services may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. We cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when using these features. To request removal of your personal information from these areas of the Services, you may contact us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
o Other Parties With Your Express or Implied Consent: We may share information with third parties when you consent to such sharing. For example, if you win a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask your permission to publicly post certain information on the Services identifying you as the winner.
o Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographic and usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations.
4. Social Networking Services
We have worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services. For example, you can use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Facebook, Google+, and others to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services.
You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Facebook, Google+, Yahoo!) to an account through our Services. This may allow you to use your credentials from the other site or service to sign in to certain features on our Services. If you link your account from a third-party site or service, we may collect your personal information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
5. Links to Other Websites
The Services may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties and that are not under the control of or maintained by us. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. If you submit personal information to any third-party websites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to this third-party content. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third-party websites or services.
6. Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We have adopted security procedures to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the information you provide to us. For example, if we collect financial information, we will use encryption software to help protect this information when it is in transit. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com.
7. Children's Privacy
The Services do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13. If we are made aware we have collected personal information from a child under 13 years old in a manner that is inconsistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), we will delete this information as soon as possible.
8. Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Services after any modification to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the new terms. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
9. Access/Choice/Retention
You may choose to receive promotional emails, newsletters, push notifications, and similar communications from us. You may opt out of receiving commercial emails from us by clicking on the opt-out or "unsubscribe" link included in the commercial e-mails you receive. You may opt-out from text alert, by replying to the alert with "STOP" or by emailing us at the email address listed below. You may opt-out from receiving push notifications by turning them off at the device level. Please note that opt-out requests may take some time to be effective, however we will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that you request or that are not commercial in nature. For example, we may contact you concerning any purchases you have made with us, even if you opt out of receiving unsolicited commercial or marketing email messages.
Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may request that we update, amend, or delete inaccuracies, or remove certain information by signing into your account and making the required changes, by emailing our Customer Support at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com, or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 20 business days.
You may opt-out of location-based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
You may request removal of your Personal Information from our publicly accessible blogs or community forums by sending an email to digital@philadelphiaeagles.com. But please be aware that in some cases we may not be able to remove your Personal Information despite your request.
10. Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to digital@philadelphiaeagles.com or write us at Attention: Digital, Philadelphia Eagles LLC, NovaCare Complex, One NovaCare Way, Philadelphia, PA 19145.
In some cases, third parties may be able to collect information about a user's online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Services.
Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.
For California residents, please see our California Consumer Privacy Act Notice for more information about your personal information processed by us.
11. International Users
Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.
13. Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services
We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. To manage your preferences you may opt out here http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/. The Services may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. Nielsen believes that you should have a choice about whether to contribute to our research and insights. To opt out of Nielsen measurement, you need only to activate the "Limit Ad Tracking" (for iOS devices) or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" (for Android devices) option in your devices settings. For web, please visit: http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy to learn more about the Nielsen digital measurement products and your choices in regard to them.
12. Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Services, please contact us by email at digital@philadelphiaeagles.com or by regular mail at
Philadelphia Eagles LLC
NovaCare Complex
One NovaCare Way
Philadelphia, PA 19145
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
Big left arrow icon
Big right arrow icon
Close icon
InstagramTwitterFacebookSnapchatShop IconProfile Overlay
AvatarAddAirplayArrow LeftArrow RightArrow UpArrow DownAudioBack 5sBack 10sBack 30sCalendarChartCheckDownLeftRightUpChromecast OffChromecast OnCloseClosed CaptionsBench OffBench OnBroad OffBroad OnVertical OffVertical OnCommentDockDoneDownloadDraftFantasyFilterForward 5sForward 10sForward 30sFull Screen OffFull Screen OnGamepassGamesInsightsKeyLeaveLiveCombineDraftFantasyMenu GamesMenu NetworkMenu NewsMenu PlayoffsMenu Pro BowlMenu ShopMenu StandingsMenu StatsMenu Super BowlMenu TeamsMenu TicketsMenuMore HorizontalMore VerticalMy LocationNetworkNewsPauseplayMultiple PlayersSingle PlayerPlaylistPlayoffsPro BowlPurgeRefreshRemoveReplaySearchSettingsShare AndroidShare Copy URLShare EmailShare FacebookShare InstagramShare iOSShare SnapchatShare TwitterSkip NextSkip PreviousStandingsStarStatsSwapTeamsTicketsVideoVisibility OffVisibility OnVolume HiVolume LowVolume MediumVolume MuteWarningWebsite
Caret downCaret upAt
The browser you are using is no longer supported on this site. It is highly recommended that you use the latest versions of a supported browser in order to receive an optimal viewing experience. The following browsers are supported: Chrome, Edge (v80 and later), Firefox and Safari.
Got it!
